http://www.buzzback.com/privacy?hsLang=en

Combined Shape
Created with Sketch.
Effective June 12, 2018, “BuzzBack will not reveal a member’s identity or contact information unless the member authorizes and gives consent for us to do so.” BuzzBack has implemented a number of policies to support our Privacy Promise. To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy we have disclosed our information management and privacy policies below. This information is meant to help you better understand:
This privacy statement covers the domains of buzzback.com and panel.buzzback.com.
What information this Website gathers from you and how that information is used
Which information may be shared and with whom
The kind of security procedures that are in place to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of information under BuzzBack control
What choices are available to you regarding the collection, use, and distribution of the information
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information
BuzzBack legal responsibilities regarding personal information
BuzzBack’s policy regarding children’s privacy
How you will be notified of any changes to BuzzBack Privacy Policies
What you can do if you feel that BuzzBack is not abiding by our posted Privacy Promise
If you feel that BuzzBack is not abiding by our posted Privacy Promise, you should contact our BuzzBack Privacy Director by email at privacy@buzzback.com.
EU-U.S. Privacy Shield
BuzzBack LLC (and its subsidiary company(ies) [such as*] BuzzBack Ltd, etc.] participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework.  BuzzBack is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List.
BuzzBack is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf.  BuzzBack complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.
With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, BuzzBack is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.  In certain situations, BuzzBack may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.
Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website, you may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.
What information this website gathers from you
BuzzBack collects information from several different areas of our website.
Registration and Participation in BuzzBack Sessions
In order to use this website, users must first complete the registration form and provide some personal information including demographic information and contact information. BuzzBack uses your demographic information (such as age, gender, etc.) to invite you to appropriate research sessions. We also use the demographic information you submit to interpret the results of our research. (For example, if we did a survey on television watching habits we might report that 60% of single people watch TV at least 3 days a week.) BuzzBack uses your contact information (such as name, email address, and postal address) to invite you to participate in BuzzBack sessions and to pay you for your participation. BuzzBack will not disclose your identity or any of your personally identifiable information without your authorization.
Cookies
BuzzBack and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer its website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.  Cookies are small text files which are transferred from our websites, applications or services and stored on your device. We use cookies to help us provide you with a personalized service, and to help make our website, applications and services better for you… BuzzBack serves session cookies only. Once the user closes his or her browser, the session is ended and the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. We may also use cookies to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Users who reject cookies will have limited use of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in a BuzzBack research session.
Log Files
We use IP addresses, browser type, referring URLs, operating system, and date/time stamp to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in optimizing the performance of our site and our services.
Links
BuzzBack’s website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that BuzzBack is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by BuzzBack’s website.
Which information may be shared and with whom
Personal Demographic & Contact Information
As a research firm, BuzzBack shares answers to research questions with clients and partners; however, we will never reveal a user’s identity or personally identifiable information unless the user authorizes and gives consent for us to do so.
BuzzBack will report demographic data (such as age, gender, etc.) for research session participants in aggregate to BuzzBack clients or partners according to standard research practices.
Information Associated with Responses to Research Questions
Any information users give in open-ended responses to BuzzBack survey questions, in BuzzBack forums, or in live chats may be viewed by BuzzBack clients or partners.
We may share your information with third parties who provide services on our behalf to help with our business activities.  These companies are authorized to use your personal information only with your consent and only as necessary to provide these services to us.
These services may include:
Fulfilling orders and delivering products/packages
Payment processing
Sending marketing communications
Conducting research and analysis
The kind of security procedures that are in place to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of information under BuzzBack control
We do not share, sell, trade, or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. We take every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via our website, their information is protected both online and offline.
When our registration form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as their passwords), that information is hidden (ie stars – *** – appear instead of letters or numbers).
BuzzBack also does everything in its power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our computers and mobile devices are password-protected with screen-savers and required authentication when employees leave their desks. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, employees are notified and/or reminded of the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users’ information is protected.
Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure, restricted access environment.
If you have any questions about the security of our website or your personal information, you can send an email to privacy@buzzback.com.
What choices are available to you regarding the collection, use, and distribution of the information
Choice/Opt-out
We partner with a third party to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.  If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/  [or if located in the European Union click http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/].   Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.
Users who do not wish to receive information from BuzzBack may ‘opt-out’ either during registration or after registering through the Members section of our website.
If members wish to share their personally identifiable information (such as an email address) with another company which is making a special offer through BuzzBack (eg. Survey respondents can receive free samples) we will make it as clear as possible to users what information will be shared and how it will be used. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.
Site and Service Updates
We send users site and service announcement updates. On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. We communicate with users to provide requested services and in regard to issues relating to their account via email or phone.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information
Upon request BuzzBack will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You can also choose to opt out at any time.
You may access, change (such as your zip code), or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update or remove any personal data provided to us. This can be done by logging into the “My BuzzBack” page off our homepage (www.buzzback.com) or by emailing Customer Support at support@buzzback.com. You can also contact us via postal mail at:
BuzzBack LLC989 Sixth Ave, 5th floorNew York, NY 10018
BuzzBack LTDPhoenix WharfUnit 4, Upper DeckEel Pie IslandTwickenham  TW1 3DY
BuzzBack legal responsibilities regarding personal information
BuzzBack may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law or to comply with a legal process served on our website.
BuzzBack’s policy regarding children’s privacy
BuzzBack will comply with all COPPA rules and regulations. In accordance with these regulations, we will not knowingly collect any information from any individual under the age of 13 without permission from his or her parents or legal guardian.
How we notify users of any changes to BuzzBack privacy policies
If we are going to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. All users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. However, if users have opted out of all communication with BuzzBack, then they will not be contacted, nor will any personally identifiable information be used in this new manner.
What you can do if you feel that BuzzBack is not abiding by its posted Privacy Promise
If you feel that BuzzBack is not abiding by its posted Privacy Promise, you should contact BuzzBack’s Privacy Director by email at privacy@buzzback.com.
Combined Shape
Created with Sketch.
Looking for inspiring insights?
© 2020 buzzback LLC All rights reserved
Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
